<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Mores on Mich Chan 🦈</title><link>http://togarashimayo.com/more/</link><description>Recent content in Mores on Mich Chan 🦈</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 09 Jun 2023 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://togarashimayo.com/more/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Books</title><link>http://togarashimayo.com/more/books/</link><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jun 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://togarashimayo.com/more/books/</guid><description>Booklist A (mostly) up-to-date of books that I&amp;rsquo;ve read, are currently reading, or want to read.
To read Fictional Mockingjay by Suzanne Collins Klara and the Sun by Kazuo Ishiguro Heidi (original German version) by Johanna Spyri Gregs Tagebuch (Diary of a Wimpy Kid&amp;rsquo;s German translation) by Jeff Kinney Non-Fictional The 48 Laws of Power by Robert Greene The 4-Hour Workweek by Tim Ferriss Ikigai by Héctor García and Francesc Miralles Mao&amp;rsquo;s America: A Survivor&amp;rsquo;s Warning by Xi Van Fleet Digital Minimalism by Cal Newport Currently reading Struwwelpeter (original German version) by Heinrich Hoffmann Battle Royale by Koushun Takami Already read 2023 Deep Work by Cal Newport The Subtle Art of Not Giving a F*ck by Mark Manson Pachinko by Min Jin Lee The Hitchhiker&amp;rsquo;s Guide to the Galaxy by Douglas Adams Rich Woman by Kim Kiyosaki Limitless by Jim Kwik Atomic Habits by James Clear Clean Code by Robert C.</description></item><item><title>Intro to Manhwa list</title><link>http://togarashimayo.com/more/intro-to-manhwa-list/</link><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jun 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://togarashimayo.com/more/intro-to-manhwa-list/</guid><description>Intro to Manhwa list - Otakon 2023 During Otakon 2023, I ran this panel wthout any visuals, because the projector wouldn&amp;rsquo;t recognize the HDMI adapter plugged to my Surface. I also promised the list and slide deck during the panel. Here is the list (and its slide deck)
Print manhwa Full House Priest Goong/Palace Hellbound Villainess Destined to Die My recommendations (&amp;hellip;and also Emily&amp;rsquo;s) Daughter of the Emperor 50 Tea Recipes from the Duchess Remarried Empress Marry my Husband The Girl Downstairs Jungle Juice +99 Wooden Stick Orange Marmalade Itaewon Class Mom I&amp;rsquo;m Gay Taste of Illness Bastard Sweet Home Shotgun Boy Pigpen All of Us are Dead My Daughter is a Zombie Surviving Romance Iconic titles Abandoned Empress God of High School Noblesse Tower of God Solo Leveling Other Masked Girl Twilight (the graphic novel)</description></item><item><title>Other Mich Chans</title><link>http://togarashimayo.com/more/other-mich-chans/</link><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jun 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://togarashimayo.com/more/other-mich-chans/</guid><description>Other Mich Chans Dedicated to the other Mich Chans floating around the internet, whether &amp;ldquo;Mich Chan&amp;rdquo; is their legal name or their pseudonym, or &amp;ldquo;Chan&amp;rdquo; is their surname but regularly use &amp;ldquo;Mich&amp;rdquo; as their nickname.
&amp;ldquo;Mich Chan&amp;rdquo;, Mexican anime fan Mich Chan, South Australian illustrator &amp;ldquo;Mich&amp;rdquo; Chan, Malaysian weight loss coach Mich Chan, Malaysian real estate agent Mich Chan, Hong Kong legal worker and pro-Yellow protestor Mich Chan, Final Fantasy character Mich Chan, salesperson at a Hong Kong contruction materials company Nya Mich-chan, Spanish anime fanfiction writer Mich Chan, contributor to a visual novel walkthrough guide Mich Chan, Filipino cold-brew-selling business student Mich Chan Thoy, destitute Cambodian primary student Mich Chan, Indonesian foodie mich-chan, BTS and Miraculous Ladybug fan Mich Chan, Indonesian YouTuber Mich Chan, Filipino TikToker Mich Chan, Filipino Showtime Summer fan If you are a Mich Chan or know another Mich Chan, don&amp;rsquo;t hestitate to let me know.</description></item><item><title>Recommended food places</title><link>http://togarashimayo.com/more/food-suggestions/</link><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jun 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://togarashimayo.com/more/food-suggestions/</guid><description>Recommended places Vancouver Sushi Miku (nicest aburi I&amp;rsquo;ve had) Seto (&amp;ldquo;authentic&amp;rdquo; Japanese food) Sushi Aria (pricier than Samurai but has a better fish/rice ratio) Samurai Sushi (cheap sushi) Coffee and treats Aiyaohno Cafe (particularly like their milk tea and brownie) Thierry Beta 5 The Pie Hole L&amp;rsquo;OTUS Mochido Mello Earnest North America Seattle MOD Pizza Salt &amp;amp; Straw FOB Poke Bar Maneki Beanfish Momiji Toronto COPS Donuts Craig&amp;rsquo;s Cookies Baltimore / Washington DC Mera Ramen Utsuke The Charmery Prost!</description></item><item><title>Visions and goals</title><link>http://togarashimayo.com/more/visions-and-goals/</link><pubDate>Tue, 26 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://togarashimayo.com/more/visions-and-goals/</guid><description>Visions and goals My former workplace has a self-improvement program called &amp;ldquo;Visions and goals&amp;rdquo;. We&amp;rsquo;d write a vision (or two) outlining what our future would look like, before writing some short-term SMART goals to hit before a certain timeframe (in the workplace&amp;rsquo;s case, every four months or a quarter). The visions would then be published on a company-wide spreadsheet where we&amp;rsquo;d be held accountable for them near the end of each quarter.</description></item></channel></rss>